PETE LEPAGE: There's a better way
PETE LEPAGE：有更好的方法
to track the performance of your site,
跟踪您网站的效果，
forms get some new capabilities, and native lazy loading is here
表单具有一些新功能，本地延迟加载在这里
I'm Pete LePage.
我是Pete LePage。
Let's dive in and see what's new for developers in Chrome 77.
让我们深入了解Chrome 77开发人员的最新功能。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
Understanding and measuring the real world performance
了解和衡量现实世界的表现
of your website can be hard.
您的网站可能很难。
Metrics like load, DOMcontentloaded
指标（如负载，DOMcontentloaded）
don't tell you what the user is seeing on screen.
不要告诉您用户在屏幕上看到的内容。
First Paint and First Contentful Paint
第一种涂料和第一种内容丰富的涂料
only capture the beginning of the experience.
仅捕捉体验的开始。
First Meaningful Paint is better,
第一有意义的油漆更好，
but it's still complex and sometimes wrong.
但是它仍然很复杂，有时甚至是错误的。
The largest Contentful Paint API,
最大的Contentful Paint API，
available starting in Chrome 77, reports
从Chrome 77开始可用，报告
the render time of the largest element visible in the viewport
视口中可见的最大元素的渲染时间
and makes it possible to measure when
并可以测量何时
the main content of the page is loaded.
页面的主要内容已加载。
To measure the largest Contentful Paint,
为了衡量最大的Contentful Paint，
you'll need to use a Performance Observer
您需要使用性能观察器
and look for the largest Contentful Paint events.
并寻找最大的Contentful Paint事件。
Since a Paint often loads in stages,
由于Paint通常会分阶段加载，
it's possible that the largest element on a page will change.
页面上最大的元素可能会改变。
So you should only report the last, largest Contentful Paint
因此，您应该只报告最后一个最大的Contentful Paint
event to your analytic service.
事件到您的分析服务。
Phil has a great post on the largest Contentful Paint
菲尔（Phil）在最大的Contentful Paint上有出色的文章
API on web.dev.
web.dev上的API。
Many developers build custom form controls
许多开发人员构建自定义表单控件
either to customize the look and feel of existing elements
要么自定义现有元素的外观
or to build new controls that aren't built into the browser.
或构建浏览器未内置的新控件。
Typically, this involves using JavaScript and hidden input
通常，这涉及使用JavaScript和隐藏输入
elements, but it's not a perfect solution.
元素，但这不是一个完美的解决方案。
Two new web features added in Chrome 77
Chrome 77中添加了两个新的Web功能
make it easier to build custom form controls
使构建自定义表单控件更加容易
and remove many of the existing limitations.
并消除许多现有限制。
The formdata event is a low level API
formdata事件是一个低级API
that lets any JavaScript code participate
允许任何JavaScript代码参与
in a form submission.
在表单提交中。
To use it, add a formdata event listener to the form
若要使用它，请将formdata事件侦听器添加到窗体
that you want to interact with.
您想要与之互动的。
When the user clicks the Submit button,
当用户单击“提交”按钮时，
the forum fires the formdata event,
论坛触发了formdata事件，
which includes a formdata object that holds all
其中包含一个保存所有内容的formdata对象
of the data being submitted.
提交的数据。
Then in your formdata event handler,
然后在您的formdata事件处理程序中，
you can update or modify the formdata before it's submitted.
您可以在提交表单数据之前对其进行更新或修改。
FormAssociated custom elements help
FormAssociated自定义元素帮助
to bridge the gap between custom element and native controls.
弥合自定义元素和本机控件之间的差距。
It tells the browser to treat the custom element
它告诉浏览器对待自定义元素
like all other form elements and adds
像所有其他表单元素一样，并添加
common properties found on input elements,
输入元素上的常见属性，
like name, value, and validity.
例如名称，价值和有效性。
Check out the post on web.dev for all the details.
请查看web.dev上的所有详细信息。
I'm not sure how I missed native lazy loading in my last video.
我不确定在上一个视频中如何错过本地延迟加载。
It's pretty amazing.
太神奇了
So I'm including it now.
所以我现在将其包括在内。
Lazy loading is a technique that allows
延迟加载是一种允许
you to defer the loading of non-critical resources,
您推迟非关键资源的加载，
like off-screen images or iframes,
例如屏幕外图像或iframe，
until they're needed, increasing the performance of your page.
直到需要它们为止，从而提高页面的性能。
Starting in Chrome 76, the browser
从Chrome 76开始，浏览器
handles lazy loading for you without the need
无需您为您处理延迟加载
to write custom lazy loading code
编写自定义的延迟加载代码
or use a separate JavaScript library.
或使用单独的JavaScript库。
To tell the browser that you want an image or iframe lazy
告诉浏览器您要懒惰图像或iframe
loaded, use the loading="lazy" attribute.
加载后，请使用loading =“ lazy”属性。
Images and iframes that are above the fold
折叠后的图像和iframe
will load normally, and those that are below
将正常加载，而那些低于
are only fetched when the user scrolls near them.
仅当用户在其附近滚动时才获取。
Check out the post on web.dev for details.
有关详细信息，请查看web.dev上的文章。
These are just a few of the changes in Chrome 77
这些只是Chrome 77的部分更改
for developers.
对于开发人员。
Of course, there's plenty more.
当然，还有更多。
The Contact Picker API, available as an Origin trial,
Contact Picker API，可以作为Origin试用版使用，
is a new on-demand picker that allows users to select an entry
是一个新的按需选择器，允许用户选择一个条目
or entries from their contact list
或他们的联系人列表中的条目
and share limited details of the selected
并分享所选内容的有限细节
contacts with a website.
与网站联系。
And there are new measurement units
并且有新的测量单位
in the Intl.NumberFormat API.
在Intl.NumberFormat API中。
Oh, and the Chrome Dev Summit is coming up
哦，Chrome开发者峰会即将举行
on November 11 and 12.
在11月11日和12日。
It's a great opportunity to learn about the latest tools
这是学习最新工具的绝佳机会
and updates coming to the web platform
和更新进入网络平台
and hear directly from the Chrome engineering team.
并直接听取Chrome工程团队的意见。
It'll be streamed live on our YouTube channel,
它将在我们的YouTube频道上直播，
or if you want to attend in person,
或者如果您想亲自参加，
you can request your invite at the Chrome Dev Summit website.
您可以在Chrome Dev Summit网站上请求邀请。
All the details, including docs and specs,
所有详细信息，包括文档和规范，
are in the updates post linked in the description.
在描述中链接的更新帖子中。
Be sure to check out the latest Chrome DevTools video to learn
请务必查看最新的Chrome DevTools视频以了解
what's new in DevTools.
DevTools中的新功能。
And don't forget to subscribe.
并且不要忘记订阅。
I'm Pete LePage.
我是Pete LePage。
And as soon as Chrome 78 is released,
Chrome 78发布后，
I'll be right here to tell you what's new in Chrome.
我将在这里告诉您Chrome的新功能。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]